(Penny:)Hey, here's another possible
topic of conversation.
(Penny:)This is a big night for Sheldon.
(Penny:)Right, Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)Big night?
(Sheldon:)The winter solstice
is a big night.
(Sheldon:)It's over 14 hours
(Sheldon:)in Southern California.
(Amy:)That's an amusing factoid.
(Penny(spits out drink explosively. Howard types. Robot arm hands Penny a napkin):)Thank you.
(Howard:)No, no.
(Penny:)My point is, uh, tonight is
Sheldon's first official date.
(Penny:)Discuss.
(Amy:)Is this true?
(Sheldon:)Apparently, a semi-incestuous
Teens for Jesus
(Sheldon:)Fourth of July Hoedown
didn't count.
(Penny:)So, um, Amy, what about you?
(Penny:)Do you date much?
(Amy:)Once a year.
(Amy:)It's a deal I made
with my mother in exchange for
(Amy:)her silence on the matter,
as well as the occasional use
(Amy:)of her George Foreman Grill
that seals in the flavor
without the fat.
(Amy:)How about you, Penny?
(Amy:)Do you go on many dates?
(Penny:)Uh, yeah, I wouldn't say many.
(Scene:)A few.